starting and trading is something that I
would recommend anybody in the world to
do it allows you to make anywhere from
1,000 2 three even $10,000 every single
day or where I've made anywhere from 50
to even $100,000 a day with just 1 to
two hours of dedication into the craft
but however it's not something that is
going to come overnight obviously making
$100,000 in one day it's not going to
happen in just a snap of a finger for
you to learn this skill set it takes
extreme dedication and a very strong
mindset and once you have mastered this
skill set that there's absolutely no
limmit to what you can do and what you
can scale your life to do the trading
and personally for me to even see $1 in
return from my investment into trading
it took me about 2 and 1/2 years
literally took Me 2 and 1/2 years to
become a successful Trader or what I
considered it was at the time but
however it could have happened in a much
shorter time I could have easily become
a profitable Trader in the first four to
5 months if I would have avoided these
deadly four points that I'm going to be
discussing in this video right here
which these de mistakes is what 99% of
Traders do when they get started in the
industry I'm victim of it and so is
pretty much everybody out there that got
started and if you watch this video to
the end you're going to have so much
Clarity on what mistakes to avoid and so
much time is going to be saved so that
leads me to my first point which is
going to be only focused on one market
yes there's so many different markets
out there to trade you have Futures
indices Forex crypto stocks bonds
anything with a graph realistically you
can trade but one of the big biggest
mistakes that a Trader makes is called
the shiny object syndrome you see every
Market out there and you want to trade
every single Market out there because
you think the more you trade the more
markets you're involved in the more
money you will make and that is actually
completely wrong less is more in this
industry I realized when I dialed in in
only one specific Market in one specific
pair everything completely changeed for
me because if you're focused on 100
things at the same time you're simply
not going to have any growth so one of
the the biggest points that I can say is
stick to a market whether it's Futures
whether it's Forex whether it's cryptos
stick to one and do not leave from it
give it some time for the strategy to
develop and for you to have a learning
progress with it that way you can learn
from your mistakes and you can see
patterns happen in the market
consistently so then you can capitalize
off of it but you will never see a
pattern in the market where you can
capitalize off of it again if you're
always switching markets back and forth
and just put this into perspective
learning trading is like learning a
different language every different
Market is like a different language
let's say Futures is English indices is
Spanish crypto is Russian Forex is
Italian and let's say you're trying to
learn all these languages at the same
time the probability of you learning any
of these language fluently is probably
slim to none because everything is so
confusing so whatever language you think
you're going to use most whether it's
Spanish cuz you're always going to be in
Latin America whether it's English
because you want to move to the USA just
stick to that that language and once you
master it then you can move on to a new
language but don't focus on so many
languages at the same time because you
simply won't get them it's just not
going to work so to keep it simple pick
one market I picked the Forex market and
thanks to that I've been able to make 50
even $100,000 in one single day and
actually to add it to that point same
way how you pick a language you have to
pick a teacher that's going to teach you
that language right you can obviously
learn online and you can watch ecourses
but those ecourses somebody's teaching
you you have to pick one teacher so you
can learn the language that way so then
you learn their accent so on and so
forth it's the same exact thing with
trading whenever you find your Mentor
you find your teacher you find your
educator whoever is going to teach you
this new language of trading stick to it
just because this teacher either talks a
little bit slow or maybe you don't
understand them at first give it a shot
I say always give a mentor or a teacher
at least 6 months for you to understand
and learn this new craft because
remember you're starting from Ground
Zero it's obviously going to be
confusing at the beginning and it's
going to be frustrating but you can't
just quit within the first two weeks and
not give the teacher the benefit of the
doubt you have to find a teacher that
relates to you that motivates you and
that most importantly has results
because that way they know what they're
talking about and then they're going to
know that what they're going to teach
you is going to make sense so same way
how you're going to stick to one market
you need to stick to one Mentor so you
just shorten your learning curve so much
because I personally had about eight
different mentors and I did not become
profitable until I didn't just just
stick to one and I'm sure I could have
stuck to any of the eight mentors that I
used at the beginning but I never gave
them more than two three weeks of
teaching to give the strategy a chance
but as soon as I got tired of looking
for other mentors I'm like you know what
I'm just going to stick with this guy
and see what what happens and would you
look at that after 6 months of
consistent mentoring by this educator I
became a profitable Trader and this is
not only my case this is why when I get
on my weekly calls with my students I'm
so consistent with them every single
week I get on a call with the students
and I break down my top three top four
players that I trade for the week to
show them that the consistency is the
key to success because a lot of other
Educators out there they just you know
have a pre-recorded course and that's it
but I personally I have a weekly
mentorship call where I teach you not
only how to trade but then how to trade
with me and then we you know talk about
it in the Discord and stuff because the
real key to success here is the
consistency and giving the strategy you
know time to play out and for you to
actually learn how to use it into the
market and how to capitalize with it so
now moving on the next point and this is
something that I am a victim of when I
started having what I considered was big
results and that is sticking to your
trading plan a lot of Traders they pass
their first challenge they flip their
first account they make their first
dollars in the market they get the feel
of the money and you feel like you're
the king of the world you feel like
you're on top of the world you're
Invincible this is probably one of the
most deadliest moments that you can ever
have in your trading career because now
that you've made some money in the
market you feel Invincible a losing
streak is right ahead of you because
you're you're going to now approach the
market with a different trading plan
because you're getting comfortable and
now you lose a couple of Trades you lose
your winning streak and then now you're
questioning your whole life your whole
existence because everything went down
to drain so whenever you start making
money in the markets whether it's a lot
or a little do absolutely nothing I get
the question asked all the time or like
hey I just passed my challenge I got
funded and I'm on a fifth payout what
should I change to scale and get bigger
and my is absolutely nothing you've
cracked the code you're already making
money now what's going to take you to
scale and to make more money and manage
larger funds is simply time and you know
getting more challenges and accumulating
more profits and compounding over time
but do not change one single thing that
you have been doing for the last 6
months to a year whatever time it is for
you to get those results that is the key
to being consistent don't fix something
that is simply not broken and a lot of
people think that the losses get people
down no it's actually once people have
that rise and they get hit with reality
and then they fall back down that's
where they start requestioning their
whole entire existence and trying to now
chain strategy chain mentors and it's
just a downward spiral effect that could
have simply been saved by just sticking
to the plan don't fix something that's
not broken and now finally my favorite
one there is no such thing as getting
rich quick I know a lot of these people
on social media make it look so easy to
make money by clicking a couple buttons
I am a victim of that I remember when I
started trading and I was looking at the
profitable Traders or the successful
traders of the time and I see them
making 20 $30,000 a day I'm like damn
all I need is just 10% of that and I'll
be happy and the reality of the
situation is that that's a lie cuz once
you do make those profits you're never
satisfied with but that's a whole other
conversation the point is that stop
trying to take 100 bucks to a million
doll obviously I tried this and I you
know succeeded to a certain point but I
ended up blowing it I took $100 to
300,000 and almost 3 months and then I
blew it and I did that documented out
here on YouTube to show you guys that it
is not a sustainable type of Market
approach is it a reality yes you can do
it definitely the opportunity is there
it's not impossible but it's not
sustainable so stop trying to get rich
quick the goal should be for you to
learn the craft and as soon as you learn
the craft and Master it you know
everything about it the money will come
on its own and I can guarantee you that
myself I was literally just I I just did
that Challenge 100 to the mill just to
show you guys that all you need is a
profitable strategy once you have the
profitable strategy you can challenge
yourself to do absolutely anything so
completely eliminate making money right
away and focus on learning the craft and
everything about it right away and keep
in mind the person that I am today is
not the same person that I was five six
years ago when I started trading I was
smoking weed working at Dunkin' Donuts
waking up late I just wasn't the same
person in order for you to become a
profitable Trader as crazy as this might
sound you have to turn into a completely
new person because the habits that you
have right now the routine that you have
right now and your beliefs right now
simply don't align with the requirements
of becoming a profitable Trader and
that's just the simple truth the power
printing money from anywhere in the
world where you want simply comes with a
certain amount of skill sets and it
comes with a St status that comes with
it yes anybody can do it but you have to
reach those status and those
expectations that the market requires so
every profitable Trader out there that
you see they've had to have a huge
change in their personal life and their
routine life I can guarantee you that
and these are just one of my biggest
dead points that if I would have learned
at the beginning of trading I would have
saved myself easily one one and a/ half
years of endless questions endless of
doubts in my journey and I really hope
hope you guys have learned from this
because if you can just apply 50% of
what this video teaches you you will
exponentially shorten your learning
curve and the mistakes that you have
made like I have taken my students that
literally know nothing from Trading and
they start generating anywhere from a
th000 to
$1,500 a week with my set and forget
strategy in the first three months don't
take my word for it there's thousands of
Traders out there that are using the set
and forget strategy on a day-to-day
basis we got on a call every single week
where I explain to you the top pairs
that I personally trade and we trade
together you also meet other like-minded
people so if you want to know more about
the center forget strategy and if you
want to basically talk to me every
single week and ask me any questions you
want make sure to hit the link in the
description below I have a video that
explain to you what the set and forget
strategy consists you guys it might be a
little bit intimidating at the beginning
seeing somebody make anywhere from 50 to
100K a day but as crazy as it might
sound this has turned into the new
normal and students making anywhere from
$1,000 to $11,500 a week is actually the
normal inside deci and forget community
so if you want to know more about it hit
the link in the description below
appreciate you guys watching all the
vide to the end and I'll see you guys in
the next video